A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, 2002-2009 (bulk 2005-2009)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, 2002-2009 (bulk 2005-2009)
The Library of Virginia
44683
9.2 cu.ft. (26 boxes)
Virginia. Office of the Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected information is considered closed for 75 years after date of record creation. Types of records restricted include but are not limited to: Attorney-client privilege materials and social security numbers. Restricted information has been sealed, but has not been removed from the collection.
Acquisition Information
Transferred by the Office of the Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, 1111 East Broad Street, Room 4082, Richmond, Virginia, 23219, 13 January, 2010.
Historical Information
Finally established in 2004, the eventual creation of the Agriculture and Forestry secretariat began with a 2001 gubernatorial campaign promise made by Governor Mark R. Warner to provide cabinet level representation for the agriculture and forestry industry. Further support for the creation of the secretariat came from the Governor's Agriculture Net Receipts Work Group, a task force created in 2003 by Governor Warner through the Secretary of Commerce and Trade. The goal of the task force was to determine strategies and recommendations for doubling the net profits of Virginia's agricultural sector between 2004 and 2014. Among the task force's recommendations was the creation of the, "Office of Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry to provide focus and emphasis in the development of the agriculture and forest industries." In 2004, the General Assembly of Virginia created the cabinet position of Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry with the passing of Senate Bill SB 543 and witnessed its codification through 2.2-203.3 of the Code of Virginia. Speaking at the appointment ceremony of the first Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, Governor Warner reiterated his commitment to, "support and expand our agriculture and forestry industries" and recalled his desire to, "make sure these very important sectors of Virginia's economy received a seat at my cabinet table."
The Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry is appointed by the Governor, confirmed by the General Assembly, and serves at the Governor's pleasure. It is the secretary's responsibility to oversee several agencies and other entities that formerly reported to the Office of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade. Among the agencies reporting to the Agriculture and Forestry secretariat are the Virginia Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services, the Department of Forestry, the Virginia Agricultural Council, and the Virginia Marine Products Board. The Governor may assign or reassign agencies to and from the Agriculture and Forestry secretariat through the use of executive orders. The secretary's role in leading agencies within the Agriculture and Forestry secretariat is to provide guidance and direction, "in the conservation, protection, and development of Virginia's agricultural and forest resources and in protecting the Virginia Consumer."
In December of 2004, Governor Warner appointed former Delegate Robert S. Bloxom (R-Accomack) to serve as the first Virginia Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry. Prior to his appointment, Bloxom served in the General Assembly from 1978 until his 2003 retirement and sat on the Agriculture, Labor and Commerce, and Chesapeake and its Tributaries committees. William P. Dickinson Jr., Assistant Commissioner of the Virginia Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services, was appointed to serve under Bloxom in the role of Deputy Secretary. On 29 December 2005, Governor-elect Timothy Kaine reappointed Bloxom as Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry.
Scope and Content
Records, 2002-2009 (bulk 2005-2009), created and maintained by Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, Robert S. Bloxom, during the administration of Governor Timothy M. Kaine (2006-2010). The records include agendas, correspondence, memorandum, newspaper clippings, presentations, programs, reports, speeches, studies, and other working papers. Also included are incoming and outgoing correspondence with constituents and subject files of Deputy Director, William P. Dickinson.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Subject files, 2002-2009
Series II: Constituent correspondence, 2006-2009
Series III: Deputy Director Subject files, 2004-2008
Related Material
Office of the Governor-Tim Kaine
A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine Administration Electronic Files, Email, 2002-2010 (bulk 2006-2009). The Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry Electronic Files series documents the electronic communication of the office during the Kaine administration. This series contains 1369 emails in three (3) subseries. Subseries have been designated for: A. Robert Bloxom Email; B. Charles Green Email; and C. Tracy Campbell Email. There are four privacy protected and confidential emails in this PST file that are restricted for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78. Types of restricted information includes attorney-client privilege and personnel records. The PST files for Bill Dickinson, Deputy Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, and Shauna Chavis, Executive Assistant to the Secretary, were both empty. However email messages sent by Dickinson and Chavis may be found in the email files of other members of the administration. The Library of Virginia Email Project - Governor Tim Kaine Portal provides access to the Kaine email collection and includes guides to other Kaine administration records.
The Governor Tim Kaine Administration Web Archive Collection, 2006-2010 contains archived versions of websites for the Governor's Office, his initiative sites, and the sites of his cabinet secretaries. Also included are the related sites for the First Lady (Anne Holton), as well as the Lt. Governor (Bill Bolling), and Attorney General (Bob McDonnell and William C. Mims), two statewide officials elected in the same cycle as Governor Kaine.
The Timothy M. Kaine Administration (2006-2010) Cabinet Weekly Reports Digital Collection contains the weekly reports submitted to the Governor and Chief of Staff by the Governor's Cabinet, including the Secretaries of Administration (Viola Baskerville), Agriculture and Forestry (Robert S. Bloxom), Commerce and Trade (Patrick O. Gottschalk), Commonwealth (Daniel C. LeBlanc, Jan-Mar. 2006 and Katherine K. Hanley (Mar. 2006-2010), Education (Dr. Thomas R. Morris), Finance (Jody Wagner, 2006-2008 and Richard D. Brown, 2008-2010), Health and Human Resources (Marilyn Tavenner), Natural Resources (Preston Bryant), Public Safety (John W. Marshall), Technology (Aneesh Chopra, 2006-2009 and Leonard M. Pomata, 2009-2010), and Transportation (Pierce Homer). Also included are reports by the Assistant to the Governor for Commonwealth Preparedness (Robert Crouch), Office of Constituent Services (Marc Cheatham, 2006-2007 and Amber Amato, 2007-2010), Press Office, Policy Office and Virginia Liaison Office. Reports were submitted each Thursday and placed in a binder for the Governor that he took with him at the end of the day on Friday. A second copy of the report was made for the Chief of Staff. The level of detail varied for each cabinet officer and items of importance were highlighted by staff for the Governor. Each report contains information on legislation, Governor's initiatives/special projects, agency matters/operations, events/agency visits, audits/investigations/compliance, stakeholder issues and pending decisions. Governor Kaine wrote handwritten notes and/or marked-up some reports with post-it notes and requested follow up information from the person submitting the report. Those questions and answers are included in this series. This series provides a weekly account of the issues and policy decisions of the Kaine Administration.
Contents List
- Series I: Subject files, 2002-2009., Extent: 17 boxes (5.95 cu. ft.).
  Series I: Subject files, 2002-2009, is housed in 17 boxes and arranged alphabetically by folder title. This series contains agendas, correspondence, newspaper clippings, programs, reports, speeches, studies, and other working papers. Included are subject files relating to agricultural industries such as the dairy, equine, milk, peanut, pork, potato, poultry, tomato, and wine industries, among others. Included are files on the Chesapeake Bay, farmland preservation, animal breeding, logging, establishment of state forests and parks, weights and measures programs, water conservation, organic farming, insects and pesticides, and other agriculture and forestry subjects. Also included are folders relating to trade missions to India and Cuba and speeches and visits to farms and wineries across the state.
  - Agribusiness, 2006-2009. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural Enterprise Act (HB 1947; HB 2128), 2005. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Forum with Senator Mark Warner, 2009. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural Research and Extension Center, 2009. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agricultural Stewardship Act, 2008. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agricultural Summit, 2006-2008. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agritourism, 2007-2008. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agroterrorism, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Albemarle Cider Works, 2009. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Animal Control Officers, 2006-2009. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Appalachian Sustainable Development, 2006-2007. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Apples, 2005-2007. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Appomattox-Buckingham State Forest, 2006-2008. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Arbor Day, 2007-2008. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts report, 2005-2008. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bio Mass, 2009. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bio Mass, 2009. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Big Woods Land Acquisition (Sussex Co., Va.), 2005-2009. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bioplastics, 2009. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Biosolids, 2007-2008. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Boulevard Flower Gardens (Colonial Heights, Va.), 2007. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Broadband in Eastern Shore, 2006-2007. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Burn ban, 2007-2008. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Capital outlay progress, 2005-2008. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Channels State Forest (Russell and Washington Co., Va.), 2005-2008. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Charitable Gaming Board, 2006-2007. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Charitable Gaming Board, 2008-2009. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chatham Vineyards (Northampton Co., Va.), 2006. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cheese regulations, 2005. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel, 2006-2008. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chesapeake Bay Executive Council, 2006-2008. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Chesapeake Bay Executive Council, 2009. (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
  - Chesapeake Bay watershed meeting, 2009. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Climate change and forestland conversation, 2008. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Commercial feed, 2002-2006. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Commonwealth preparedness, 2006-2009. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, General, 2006-2007. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, General, 2008. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, General, 2009. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Cows to Condoes, 2009. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Crop insurance, 2007. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Cuba trade mission, 2005-2008. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dairy industry, 2005-2009. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Department of Environmental Quality, 2006-2007. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Dogs, Commercial dog breeders (HB 538), 2008-2009. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Dogs and puppy mills, 2007-2008. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Dogs, State Veterinarian, 2007-2009. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Dragon Run State Forest (King and Queen County, Va.), 2009. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Lucy's Cookies (Norfolk, Va.), 2008. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Drought, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Dry Mill Winery and Vineyards (Leesburg, Va.), 2009. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Eastern Shore Cabinet Community Day, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Shore Pandemic Influenza Summit, 2006. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Economic Development and Natural Resources Subcommittee, 2009. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Economic Development Strategic Plan, 2006. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Economic Impart of Agriculture and FOrestry on the Commonwealth of Virginia, 2006. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Economic Impart of Agriculture and FOrestry on the Commonwealth of Virginia, 2008. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Ecosystem Services Conference, 2009. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Emergency Management, 2006-2009. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Energy research and development, 2006-2007. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Equine industry study, 2004-2008. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Executive Directive 5, Credit freeze, 2007-2009. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Executive Directive 5, Meeting brief, 2007. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Executive Directive 5, Notice of breach, 2007. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Executive Directive 5, Privacy, 2006-2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Farmland preservation, 2006-2009. (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
  - Farm ponds, 2006-2009. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Farm to School, 2007. (Box 7, Folder 2-4)
  - Federation of Virginia Food Banks, 2006. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Fire ants, 2007-2009. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Fort Valley Nursery (Woodstock, Va.), 2006-2008. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Foundation for Virginia's Natural Resources, 2005-2006. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Foundation for Virginia's Natural Resources, 2007-2008. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Forest conservation, 2006-2009. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Forest Fire Suppression and Report, 2006-2008. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Forest inventoried roadless areas, 2005-2009. (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Forestry in Virginia tours, 2005-2006. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Forestry LEED (Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design), 2008. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Forestry miscellaneous, 2005. (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Forestry miscellaneous, 2006. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Forestry miscellaneous, 2007-2009. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Fruit and vegetable commodity grading fees, 2005-2006. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - George Washington and Jefferson National Forests, 2006-2008. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Glen Manor Vineyard (Front Royal, Va.), 2008. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Goodall Property (Highland Co., Va.), 2005-2006. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Cabinet Community Day, 2007-2008. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Governor Kaine's Mission to Canada, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - H1N1, 2007-2009. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Harrionburg (Va.) Lab and Office Complex, 2006-2007. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Health Care Commission, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Hydrilla, 2006-2009. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - IFRIS Fire Protection, 2006-2008. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - India trade mission, 2007. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - International Farm Transition Network, 2008. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - International trade, 1980, 2007-2009. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Jamestown (Va.) Easter Egg presentation, 2007. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - LandCare, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Matthews State Forest (Galax, Va.), 2005-2008. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - McIntire-Stennis Cooperative Forestry Research Program, 2009. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Mead Westvaco Land, 2007. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Meat inspections, 2007-2009. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Migrants, 2007-2009. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Milk Commission, 2003. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Montague Farms (Windsor, Va.), 2006-2008. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Mountain Rose Vineyard (Wise Co., Va.), 2005-2008. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - NASA, 2007-2008. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - National Animal ID, 2005-2007. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - National Resources Summit, 2004-2006. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Nature Conservancy, 2006-2009. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Non-perpetual easements, 2005. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Non-point source, 2006-2009. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Northampton County (Va.) Agriculture, 2005-2006. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - NOIRA confined space for agriculture, 2007-2008. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Office of Consumer Affairs, 2004-2005. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Office of Consumer Affairs, 2006-2007. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Office of Consumer Affairs, 2008-2009. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Oliver Hill Building (Richmond, Va.), 2006. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Open Kitchen (Falls Church, Va.), 2009. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Organic Farming, 2008. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Outlying Landing Field (OLF) Surry Co., Va., 2008-2009. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Peaker Plant (Accomack Co., Va.), 2009. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Peanuts, 2006-2008. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Performance Management reports, 2007-2008. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Persimmon tree companies, 2009. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Pesticide, 2006-2009. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Phragmites, 2008. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Poplar Hollow Gun Club, 2008. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Pork Industry, 2006-2009. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Potatoes, 2006. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Potomac Point Winery (Stafford Co., Va.), 2007. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Poultry Industry, 2006-2009. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Poultry Industry, 2006-2009>. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Private property rights, 2009. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Project Learning Tree, 2006. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Purchase of Development Rights (PDR), 2004-2009. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate DRES, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Reforestation of timberlands, 2009. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Riparian rights (HB 1185), 2006. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Rogers, et al vs. Dow AgroSciences et al, 2005-2006. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Roscoe Reynolds stimulus, 2009. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Rural Summit, 2008-2009. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Scottsville (Va.) Center for the Arts and Nature, 2007-2008. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Scrapie eradication regulations, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Seafood Industry, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Senate Committee on Agriculture, Conservation, and Natural Resources, 2007-2009. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Senate Finance Subcommitee, 2006-2008. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 367, 2005-2007. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Simply Fresh, LLC (Timberville, Va.), 2006. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Small Business Development Center for Virginia Farmers, 2007. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Small Women and Minority Owned (Swam), 2007-2009. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Soil fumigants, 2006-2008. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Soybean Rust, 2005-2007. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Speciality agriculture, 2005-2008. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2006-2009. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Stewardship Virginia Project, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Studies, 2006-2007. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Tech innovation, 2008. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Telework, 2008. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Tomato Industry, 2007-2009. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - USDA Farm Service Agency (Va.), 2006-2009. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - USDA Rural tours, 2009. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Agriculture Council, 2007-2008. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Association of Resource Conservation and Development, 2005-2008. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - VDACS Annual Report on the Consumer Affairs Activities, 2006-2007. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - VDACS Continuity of Government Plan, 2007. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - VDACS Export Strategy Task Force, 2006. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - VDACS Report of Accomplishments, 2006. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Farm Link Program, 2009. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Farmers Market System, 2006-2008. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - "Virginia Finest" Program, 2004-2006. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Forest Watch, 2005-2009. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Forestry Association, 2006-2007. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Horse Center Foundation, 2005-2006. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - VITA, 2007-2009. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation, 2006-2009. (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
  - Virginia Loggers Association, 2009. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Marine Products Board, 2005-2008. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Riparian Buffer and Virginia Stream Alliance Annual Report, 2005. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Tech (Blacksburg, Va.), 2005-2009. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Vineyards Association, 2007. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Voters for Animal Welfare, 2006-2008. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Wildland Fire Academy, 2009. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Waste Management, 2007-2008. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Water regulations and standards, 2006-2009. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Water Stewardship, Inc., 2008. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Waverly Particleboard (Waverly, Va.), 2007-2008. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Weights and Measures Program, 2005. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Weights and Measures Program, 2005-2007. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Weights and Measures Program, 2007-2008. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - White Birch Paper Company (Greenwich, CT), 2006-2007. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Wine Industry (HB1435), Analysis, 2006-2007. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Wine Industry (HB1435), Final report, 2006-2007. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Wine Industry (HB1435), Independent case study, 2006. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Wine Industry (HB1435), Relation between counties and farm wineries report, 2006. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Wine Industry (HB1435), Miscellaneous, 2007. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Wine Industry, General, 2005-2007. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Wine Industry, General, 2006-2007. (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
  - Wine Industry, General, 2007. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Wine Industry, General, 2007-2009. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Youth Venture, Inc., 2007. (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Series II: Constituent correspondence, 2006-2009., Extent: 7.5 boxes (2.65 cu. ft.).
  Series II: Constituent correspondence, 2006-2009, is housed in 7.5 boxes and arranged numerically by control number. This series contains incoming correspondence from constituents and other non-governmental entities sent directly to the Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry or referred to the Secretary from the Office of the Governor for response. Also included is the outgoing correspondence from the Secretary as well as supporting documentation and correspondence from related agency officials. The series addresses a broad number of topics including but not limited to concern over gasoline prices, calls for legislation regarding issues of agriculture and forestry, concern over pesticide usage, drought disaster declarations, complaints against apartment landlords and automobile dealers, calls for land conservation programs, animal abuse and welfare, complaints against credit cards and payday loan programs, Eat Local initiatives, and small business owner issues.
  - 2567603-2576916, 2006 January-February. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 2577686-2588530, 2006 March. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 2589488-2592195, 2006 April. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 2592806-2594269, 2006 April. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - 2594642-2599012, 2006 May. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - 2599884-2612000, 2006 June-July. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - 2612145-2617468, 2006 August. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - 2617599-2620827, 2006 September. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - 2621369-2624573, 2006 October. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - 2625571-2634123, 2006 November-December. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 2634290-2640289, 2007 January. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 2640315-2640584, 2007 January. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 2640600-2641803, 2007 January. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - 2641818-2645694, 2007 February. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - 2647506-2651336, 2007 February. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 2651337-2660781, 2007 March. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - 2661070-2667793, 2007 March-April. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 2661717-2669046, 2007 April. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - 2669506-2672021, 2007 May. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 2672084-2674708, 2007 May. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - 2675390-2680713, 2007 June. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - 2681002-2686685, 2007 July. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - 2687218-2688454, 2007 August. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - 2688533-2689897, 2007 August. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - 2689952-2690967, 2007 August. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 2691137-2692930, 2007 August-September. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 2693002-2694996, 2007 September. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - 2695040-2697930, 2007 September-October. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 2698483-2699994, 2007 October. (Box 21, Folder 5)